wearepopslags.com 2008-12-24

# We Are Pop Slags Privacy Policy - We are committed to protecting your personal p

We are committed to protecting your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our policies on privacy. If you have any requests or queries at any time concerning your personal information or our practices, please contact us at [info@wearepopslags.com.](mailto:info@wearepopslags.com.)

**1.     What information do we collect?**  
When you visit our website, we collect information automatically about your visits, such as browsing patterns, but information collected this way is only used to aggregate form rather than being linked to identifiable individuals.

From time to time we may ask you to supply personal information in order to provide you with services (such as the forum, email newsletter and competitions). In order to deliver such services, we will need to process and store your personal information and may need to transfer it to the relevant partner(s). By submitting your personal information, you consent to our Privacy Policy. 

We seek to comply with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. We follow appropriate security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information so as to prevent unauthorised access by third parties. However, the internet is not a totally secure medium and you acknowledge and agree that we shall not be responsible for any unauthorised use, distribution, damage or destruction of personal data.

 **3rd party involvement**  
Occasionally a third party may sponsor a promotion, offer, competition or page of the website and you may be asked to provide personal information or to answer questions in order to participate. In those circumstances we may transfer personal information to those named third parties that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy policy will apply.

If you enter any competitions on this website it may be necessary for us to provide your personal information to the promoters of the competition or to others that are involved in the organisation of the competition or the prize-giving.

 **Message board**  
If you post any personal information to any forums, this information will immediately be made available to other users throughout the world who may use it to send you unsolicited communications. Furthermore, in some circumstances we may display some of your personal information (such as username) when you post material to the website to allow users to identify each other. At the point of providing personal information, we will advise you of what information may be displayed to other users.

 **2.     Cookies – what are they and how do we use them?**  
Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to your hard drive to help tailor and keep records of your visit to that website. If you visit our website, cookies help us recognise you when you visit again and allow us to better customise your visit to your individual preferences, helping us provide you with the best possible service on our Website. 

Most major websites use cookies and their use is standard on the internet. Please note: most internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can instruct your browser not to accept cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies from the sites you visit. If you decide not to accept our cookies, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site.

For further information on cookies and how to switch them off see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "All About Cookies"). 

**3\. Links**  
This site contains links and references to other websites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and our privacy policy does not apply to these sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and terms and conditions of linked or referenced sites you enter.

 **4\. International data transfer**  
The use of a website to collect and process personal information inevitably involves the transmission of data internationally. Please note that if you are based within the European Economic Area ("EEA") the information you provide may be transferred outside of the EEA for the purposes of processing by us. By visiting our website you acknowledge this and agree to the transmission of data in this way. 

If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy you should not submit your personal information on this website.
